[
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question": "What begins with A? Can you think of a fruit that starts with A?",
  "ans1": "apple",
  "ans2": "apricot",
  "ans3": "ananas",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "apple",
  "quiz_img": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question": "Can you think of a colour that starts with B?",
  "ans1": "blue",
  "ans2": "bottle",
  "ans3": "brush",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "blue",
  "quiz_img": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question": "Can you think of a piece of furniture that starts with C?",
  "ans1": "chair",
  "ans2": "coffee",
  "ans3": "cat",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "chair",
  "quiz_img": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question": "Can you think of an animal that starts with D?",
  "ans1": "door",
  "ans2": "duck",
  "ans3": "doll",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "duck",
  "quiz_img": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question": "Can you think of a body part that starts with E?",
  "ans1": "egg",
  "ans2": "eyes",
  "ans3": "elephant",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "eyes",
  "quiz_img": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question": "Can you think of a musical instrument that starts with F?",
  "ans1": "flute",
  "ans2": "fish",
  "ans3": "fire",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "flute",
  "quiz_img": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question": "Can you think of an animal that starts with G?",
  "ans1": "grass",
  "ans2": "gold",
  "ans3": "giraffe",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "giraffe",
  "quiz_img": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question": "Can you think of a body part that starts with H?",
  "ans1": "hat",
  "ans2": "hair",
  "ans3": "hill",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "hair",
  "quiz_img": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question": "Can you think of a country that starts with I?",
  "ans1": "italy",
  "ans2": "image",
  "ans3": "island",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "italy",
  "quiz_img": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question": "Can you think of a verb that starts with J?",
  "ans1": "jungle",
  "ans2": "jump",
  "ans3": "john",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "jump",
  "quiz_img": "Fun with the Alphabet!",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animal Sounds",
  "question": "A dog goes...",
  "ans1": "baah",
  "ans2": "woof",
  "ans3": "oink",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "woof",
  "quiz_img": "Animal Sounds",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animal Sounds",
  "question": "A cat goes...",
  "ans1": "moo",
  "ans2": "meow",
  "ans3": "croak",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "meow",
  "quiz_img": "Animal Sounds",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animal Sounds",
  "question": "A pig goes..",
  "ans1": "oink",
  "ans2": "moo",
  "ans3": "neigh",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "oink",
  "quiz_img": "Animal Sounds",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animal Sounds",
  "question": "A duck goes...",
  "ans1": "meow",
  "ans2": "quack",
  "ans3": "hoot",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "quack",
  "quiz_img": "Animal Sounds",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animal Sounds",
  "question": "An owl goes...",
  "ans1": "quack",
  "ans2": "moo",
  "ans3": "hoot",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "hoot",
  "quiz_img": "Animal Sounds",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animal Sounds",
  "question": "A sheep goes...",
  "ans1": "tweet",
  "ans2": "neigh",
  "ans3": "baah",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "baah",
  "quiz_img": "Animal Sounds",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animal Sounds",
  "question": "A bird goes...",
  "ans1": "meow",
  "ans2": "oink",
  "ans3": "tweet",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "tweet",
  "quiz_img": "Animal Sounds",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animal Sounds",
  "question": "A horse goes...",
  "ans1": "neigh",
  "ans2": "tweet",
  "ans3": "croak",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "neigh",
  "quiz_img": "Animal Sounds",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animal Sounds",
  "question": "A cow goes...",
  "ans1": "quack",
  "ans2": "moo",
  "ans3": "tweet",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "moo",
  "quiz_img": "Animal Sounds",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animal Sounds",
  "question": "A frog goes...",
  "ans1": "meow",
  "ans2": "quack",
  "ans3": "croak",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "croak",
  "quiz_img": "Animal Sounds",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question": "A wheel is shaped like a",
  "ans1": "circle",
  "ans2": "triangle",
  "ans3": "rectangle",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "circle",
  "quiz_img": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question": "A pizza slice is shaped like a",
  "ans1": "triangle",
  "ans2": "circle",
  "ans3": "square",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "triangle",
  "quiz_img": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question": "A shape with all four sides the same length is a",
  "ans1": "rectangle",
  "ans2": "square",
  "ans3": "triangle",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "square",
  "quiz_img": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question": "A red STOP sign is shaped like a",
  "ans1": "square",
  "ans2": "star",
  "ans3": "octagon",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "octagon",
  "quiz_img": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question": "An egg is shaped like a",
  "ans1": "triangle",
  "ans2": "oval",
  "ans3": "star",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "oval",
  "quiz_img": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question": "Rain slides off roofs that are a",
  "ans1": "triangle",
  "ans2": "square",
  "ans3": "rectangle",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "triangle",
  "quiz_img": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question": "An octagon has",
  "ans1": "eight sides",
  "ans2": "four sides",
  "ans3": "six sides",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "eight sides",
  "quiz_img": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question": "A kite is shaped like a",
  "ans1": "rectangle",
  "ans2": "diamond",
  "ans3": "circle",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "diamond",
  "quiz_img": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question": "On Valentine's day a gift is",
  "ans1": "diamond shaped",
  "ans2": "heart shaped",
  "ans3": "star shaped",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "heart shaped",
  "quiz_img": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question": "The moon is shaped like a ",
  "ans1": "circle",
  "ans2": "star",
  "ans3": "rectangle",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "circle",
  "quiz_img": "Shapes Quiz",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Colours Quiz",
  "question": "The first colour in the rainbow is",
  "ans1": "red",
  "ans2": "orange",
  "ans3": "gold",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "red",
  "quiz_img": "color-circle",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Colours Quiz",
  "question": "The colour of healthy grass is",
  "ans1": "black",
  "ans2": "green",
  "ans3": "grey",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "green",
  "quiz_img": "color-circle",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Colours Quiz",
  "question": "A very dark blue is called",
  "ans1": "pastel blue",
  "ans2": "navy blue",
  "ans3": "purple blue",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "navy blue",
  "quiz_img": "color-circle",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Colours Quiz",
  "question": "The colour of fresh snow is",
  "ans1": "green",
  "ans2": "white",
  "ans3": "beige",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "white",
  "quiz_img": "color-circle",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Colours Quiz",
  "question": "A very pale shade of brown is called",
  "ans1": "white",
  "ans2": "beige",
  "ans3": "silver",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "beige",
  "quiz_img": "color-circle",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Colours Quiz",
  "question": "When you mix red and yellow you get",
  "ans1": "orange",
  "ans2": "grey",
  "ans3": "brown",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "orange",
  "quiz_img": "color-circle",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Colours Quiz",
  "question": "A colour that is close to blue can be described as",
  "ans1": "blued",
  "ans2": "bluesy",
  "ans3": "blueish",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "blueish",
  "quiz_img": "color-circle",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Colours Quiz",
  "question": "When you mix black with white you get",
  "ans1": "gold",
  "ans2": "yellow",
  "ans3": "grey",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "grey",
  "quiz_img": "color-circle",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Colours Quiz",
  "question": "A common colour for a baby girl to wear is\r",
  "ans1": "baby blue",
  "ans2": "brown",
  "ans3": "pink",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "pink",
  "quiz_img": "color-circle",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Vocabulary Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Colours Quiz",
  "question": "The winner of an Olympic event gets a",
  "ans1": "gold medal",
  "ans2": "pink medal",
  "ans3": "blue medal",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "gold medal",
  "quiz_img": "color-circle",
  "question_img": "-"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this animal?",
  "ans1": "dog",
  "ans2": "frog",
  "ans3": "elephant",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "dog",
  "quiz_img": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "dog"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this animal?",
  "ans1": "dog",
  "ans2": "duck",
  "ans3": "monkey",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "duck",
  "quiz_img": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "duck"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this animal?",
  "ans1": "frog",
  "ans2": "sheep",
  "ans3": "elephant",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "frog",
  "quiz_img": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "frog"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this animal?",
  "ans1": "dog",
  "ans2": "elephant",
  "ans3": "sheep",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "elephant",
  "quiz_img": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "elephant"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this animal?",
  "ans1": "panda",
  "ans2": "rabbit",
  "ans3": "monkey",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "monkey",
  "quiz_img": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "monkey"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this animal?",
  "ans1": "sheep",
  "ans2": "rabbit",
  "ans3": "elephant",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "sheep",
  "quiz_img": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "sheep"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this animal?",
  "ans1": "dog",
  "ans2": "panda",
  "ans3": "rabbit",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "panda",
  "quiz_img": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "panda"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this animal?",
  "ans1": "rabbit",
  "ans2": "pig",
  "ans3": "dog",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "pig",
  "quiz_img": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "pig"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this animal?",
  "ans1": "penguin",
  "ans2": "panda",
  "ans3": "pig",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "penguin",
  "quiz_img": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "penguin"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this animal?",
  "ans1": "sheep",
  "ans2": "rabbit",
  "ans3": "elephant",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "rabbit",
  "quiz_img": "Animals Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "rabbit"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this?",
  "ans1": "skirt",
  "ans2": "pants",
  "ans3": "jacket",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "pants",
  "quiz_img": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "pants"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this?",
  "ans1": "tie",
  "ans2": "dress",
  "ans3": "hat",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "hat",
  "quiz_img": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "hat"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this?",
  "ans1": "coat",
  "ans2": "shirt",
  "ans3": "skirt",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "coat",
  "quiz_img": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "coat"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this?",
  "ans1": "jacket",
  "ans2": "dress",
  "ans3": "jeans",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "jeans",
  "quiz_img": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "jeans"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this?",
  "ans1": "hat",
  "ans2": "tie",
  "ans3": "gloves",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "tie",
  "quiz_img": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "tie"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this?",
  "ans1": "coat",
  "ans2": "shirt",
  "ans3": "jacket",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "shirt",
  "quiz_img": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "shirt"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this?",
  "ans1": "pants",
  "ans2": "dress",
  "ans3": "skirt",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "dress",
  "quiz_img": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "dress"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this?",
  "ans1": "gloves",
  "ans2": "jeans",
  "ans3": "tie",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "gloves",
  "quiz_img": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "gloves"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this?",
  "ans1": "coat",
  "ans2": "pants",
  "ans3": "jacket",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "jacket",
  "quiz_img": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "jacket"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this?",
  "ans1": "pants",
  "ans2": "dress",
  "ans3": "skirt",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "skirt",
  "quiz_img": "Clothes Picture Quiz",
  "question_img": "skirt"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fruit and Vegetable Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this food?",
  "ans1": "tomato",
  "ans2": "apple",
  "ans3": "strawberry",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "apple",
  "quiz_img": "fruit-and-vegetables",
  "question_img": "apple"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fruit and Vegetable Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this food?",
  "ans1": "grapes",
  "ans2": "mushrooms",
  "ans3": "peas",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "peas",
  "quiz_img": "fruit-and-vegetables",
  "question_img": "peas"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fruit and Vegetable Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this food?",
  "ans1": "bananas",
  "ans2": "carrot",
  "ans3": "potatoes",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "banana",
  "quiz_img": "fruit-and-vegetables",
  "question_img": "banana"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fruit and Vegetable Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this food?",
  "ans1": "apple",
  "ans2": "lemon",
  "ans3": "tomato",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "lemon",
  "quiz_img": "fruit-and-vegetables",
  "question_img": "lemon"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fruit and Vegetable Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this food?",
  "ans1": "peas",
  "ans2": "strawberry",
  "ans3": "grapes",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "grapes",
  "quiz_img": "fruit-and-vegetables",
  "question_img": "grapes"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fruit and Vegetable Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this food?",
  "ans1": "potatoes",
  "ans2": "mushrooms",
  "ans3": "bananas",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "potatoes",
  "quiz_img": "fruit-and-vegetables",
  "question_img": "potatoes"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fruit and Vegetable Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this food?",
  "ans1": "apple",
  "ans2": "strawberry",
  "ans3": "tomato",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "tomato",
  "quiz_img": "fruit-and-vegetables",
  "question_img": "tomato"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fruit and Vegetable Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this food?",
  "ans1": "potatoes",
  "ans2": "mushrooms",
  "ans3": "peas",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "mushroom",
  "quiz_img": "fruit-and-vegetables",
  "question_img": "mushroom"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fruit and Vegetable Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this food?",
  "ans1": "strawberry",
  "ans2": "tomato",
  "ans3": "grapes",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "strawberry",
  "quiz_img": "fruit-and-vegetables",
  "question_img": "strawberry"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Fruit and Vegetable Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this food?",
  "ans1": "lemon",
  "ans2": "carrot",
  "ans3": "strawberry",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "carrot",
  "quiz_img": "fruit-and-vegetables",
  "question_img": "carrot"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Jobs Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this job?",
  "ans1": "cook",
  "ans2": "artist",
  "ans3": "cleaner",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "artist",
  "quiz_img": "job-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "artist"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Jobs Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this job?",
  "ans1": "businessman",
  "ans2": "doctor",
  "ans3": "footballer",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "doctor",
  "quiz_img": "job-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "doctor"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Jobs Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this job?",
  "ans1": "cook",
  "ans2": "builder",
  "ans3": "doctor",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "cook",
  "quiz_img": "job-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "cooking"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Jobs Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this job?",
  "ans1": "firefighter",
  "ans2": "businessman",
  "ans3": "cleaner",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "cleaner",
  "quiz_img": "job-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "cleaning"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Jobs Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this job?",
  "ans1": "doctor",
  "ans2": "decorator",
  "ans3": "firefighter",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "decorator",
  "quiz_img": "job-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "decor"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Jobs Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this job?",
  "ans1": "builder",
  "ans2": "doctor",
  "ans3": "businessman",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "businessman",
  "quiz_img": "job-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "businessman"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Jobs Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this job?",
  "ans1": "policeman",
  "ans2": "cleaner",
  "ans3": "firefighter",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "firefighter",
  "quiz_img": "job-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "firefighter"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Jobs Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this job?",
  "ans1": "builder",
  "ans2": "cook",
  "ans3": "cleaner",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "builder",
  "quiz_img": "job-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "builder"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Jobs Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this job?",
  "ans1": "businessman",
  "ans2": "footballer",
  "ans3": "doctor",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "footballer",
  "quiz_img": "job-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "football"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Jobs Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this job?",
  "ans1": "cook",
  "ans2": "artist",
  "ans3": "policeman",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "policeman",
  "quiz_img": "job-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "policeman"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Furniture Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this piece of furniture?",
  "ans1": "chair",
  "ans2": "table",
  "ans3": "bed",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "bed",
  "quiz_img": "furniture-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "bed"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Furniture Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this piece of furniture?",
  "ans1": "drawer",
  "ans2": "lamp",
  "ans3": "wardrobe",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "lamp",
  "quiz_img": "furniture-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "floor-lamp"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Furniture Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this piece of furniture?",
  "ans1": "sofa",
  "ans2": "chair",
  "ans3": "armchair",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "chair",
  "quiz_img": "furniture-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "chair"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Furniture Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this piece of furniture?",
  "ans1": "table",
  "ans2": "wardrobe",
  "ans3": "sideboard",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "table",
  "quiz_img": "furniture-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "office"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Furniture Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this piece of furniture?",
  "ans1": "lamp",
  "ans2": "office chair",
  "ans3": "desk",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "office chair",
  "quiz_img": "furniture-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "desk-chair"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Furniture Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this piece of furniture?",
  "ans1": "bed",
  "ans2": "sofa",
  "ans3": "table",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "sofa",
  "quiz_img": "furniture-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "seater-sofa"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Furniture Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this piece of furniture?",
  "ans1": "wardrobe",
  "ans2": "arm chair",
  "ans3": "bed",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "wardrobe",
  "quiz_img": "furniture-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "closet"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Furniture Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this piece of furniture?",
  "ans1": "drawer",
  "ans2": "sideboard",
  "ans3": "sofa",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "drawer",
  "quiz_img": "furniture-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "drawers"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Furniture Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this piece of furniture?",
  "ans1": "table",
  "ans2": "lamp",
  "ans3": "sideboard",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "sideboard",
  "quiz_img": "furniture-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "sideboard"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Furniture Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this piece of furniture?",
  "ans1": "arm chair",
  "ans2": "office chair",
  "ans3": "chair",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "arm chair",
  "quiz_img": "furniture-pic-quiz",
  "question_img": "arm-chair"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Tools Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this tool?",
  "ans1": "screwdriver",
  "ans2": "spanner",
  "ans3": "screws",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "screwdriver",
  "quiz_img": "tool-box",
  "question_img": "screwdriver"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Tools Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this tool?",
  "ans1": "saw",
  "ans2": "pliers",
  "ans3": "hammer",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "hammer",
  "quiz_img": "tool-box",
  "question_img": "hammer"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Tools Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this tool?",
  "ans1": "tape measure",
  "ans2": "mask",
  "ans3": "toolbox",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "mask",
  "quiz_img": "tool-box",
  "question_img": "mask"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Tools Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this tool?",
  "ans1": "electric drill",
  "ans2": "screwdriver",
  "ans3": "spanner",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "electric drill",
  "quiz_img": "tool-box",
  "question_img": "drill"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Tools Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this tool?",
  "ans1": "pliers",
  "ans2": "mask",
  "ans3": "screws",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "screws",
  "quiz_img": "tool-box",
  "question_img": "bolts"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Tools Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this tool?",
  "ans1": "saw",
  "ans2": "hammer",
  "ans3": "tape measure",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "saw",
  "quiz_img": "tool-box",
  "question_img": "hand-saw"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Tools Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this tool?",
  "ans1": "electric drill",
  "ans2": "toolbox",
  "ans3": "screwdriver",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "toolbox",
  "quiz_img": "tool-box",
  "question_img": "toolbox"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Tools Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this tool?",
  "ans1": "pliers",
  "ans2": "mask",
  "ans3": "spanner",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "spanner",
  "quiz_img": "tool-box",
  "question_img": "spanner"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Tools Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this tool?",
  "ans1": "tape measure",
  "ans2": "hammer",
  "ans3": "pliers",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "tape measure",
  "quiz_img": "tool-box",
  "question_img": "tape"
 },
 {
  "type": "Picture Quizzes",
  "quiz_title": "Tools Picture Quiz",
  "question": "Can you name this tool?",
  "ans1": "screws",
  "ans2": "pliers",
  "ans3": "spanner",
  "ans4": "-",
  "correct_ans": "pliers",
  "quiz_img": "tool-box",
  "question_img": "pliers"
 }
]
